{
    "id": "51c0e243454c430a87ecce4d240d1117",
    "title": "Tenses Review Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She ....................... to church regularly.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "go",
                "goes",
                "gone"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6e4874557bf046f6a5dfbd911d976d97"
        },
        {
            "question": "Rani ...................... a cup of milk every morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "drink",
                "drinks",
                "drank"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e32508eb9a464e5ab005fbd9fb3f10d9"
        },
        {
            "question": "I usually ………………….. biographies.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "read",
                "reads",
                "reading"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "34aeeda8cd454bbfadaf61a7875d75ba"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ....................... a novel now.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "read",
                "reads",
                "am reading"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f6ee8d47d2a4435fa33d52d3304ddce1"
        },
        {
            "question": "He .....................… for competitive exams for three years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is preparing",
                "has been preparing",
                "was preparing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "00de2f6fb847423aa652fc715efdd0fb"
        },
        {
            "question": "When I reached home, my son ………………… with his toys.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "play",
                "played",
                "was playing"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5e6050b810754ed29444d148444e4fab"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ..................... . to my native place next month.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "go",
                "am going",
                "will go"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f7da4d39eace46f4b1eb0047f26ccc76"
        },
        {
            "question": "Sita ………………….. an apple in the morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "eat",
                "ate",
                "has eaten"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f150bc4357c141db893f755bb178cad5"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ...................... on the bench.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "stood",
                "stand",
                "standing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f73a963b92f54572a2bd854e98573325"
        },
        {
            "question": "He .....................… on a new novel for two years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is working",
                "has worked",
                "has been working"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c0f3ba9db4374479ac9fabc3da539685"
        }
    ]
}